• Co-founded a 501(c)(3) organization; spearheaded diversity in tech initiatives that promoted diversity and minority inclusion in the tech community at UC Berkeley. 

• Since its inception, Tequity has successfully carried out its mission by building community and providing resources for aspiring tech professionals.

• Tequity has successfully facilitated over 10 successful campus events including discussions with industry leaders from companies such as Y-Combinator, Twitter, LinkedIn, Twilio, Code2040, and more.